(Raj:)Good morning, everybody.
(Raj:)I picked up coffee
while I was out.
(Scene:)Bernadette,
here's your soy peppermint mocha.
(Bernadette:)You didn't have to do that.
(Raj:)Oh, my pleasure, and don't worry
(Raj:)about your presentation today.
You're going to be great.
Yeah, you're going to
knock it out of the park.
(Bernadette:)What presentation do I have today?
(Sheldon:)Just go.
(Raj:)He loves you.
(Howard:)What are you doing?
(Howard:)Are you trying
to make me look bad?
(Raj:)I'm just being
a good house guest.
(Howard:)No, you're being
a better husband than I am.
(Howard:)Doing the dishes,
getting coffee,
knowing about her life?
(Howard:)Who does that?
(Raj:)Oh, come on,
I brought you one, too.
(Howard:)I don't want coffee.
(Raj:)That's why I got you
hot chocolate.
(Howard:)Give me that.
(Howard:)Just stop showing me up.
(Raj:)Howard, listen to me.
(Raj:)You're a great husband.
(Raj:)Yes, your listening skills
could use some work.
(Raj:)But it's amazing
how far you've come
(Raj:)given that you're an only child
raised by an over-protective mom.